Washington Women's Arts Center 004
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
- Series 7: Exhibitions Files, 1975-1988
  - Subseries 2: Notebooks, 1977-1985
    - Printmakers VII, October 29-November 23 1985 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Craft Show, November 26-December 14 1985 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Sculpture '86, March 4-29 1986 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Interiors/Exteriors, May 3-24 1986 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Celebrations and Rituals, June 3-21 1986 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Sixteen Strong Sculpture Exhibition, October 3-29 1986? (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Juried Craft Show, November 26- December 21 1986 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Emerging Artists of Destruction, January 7- February 1 1987 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Jazz: Rhythms of the Black Community, February 6-March 1 1987 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Viewing Ourselves, April 1-26 1987 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - A Salon Comes to Willow Street, June 4-28 1987 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Art or Craft: The Fine Line, July 8- August 12 1987 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Printmakers IX, November 4-29 1987 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Contemporary Viewpoints: Crafts in Our Changing World, December 2-20 1987 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Abstractions, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Misc, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Wear Your Heart on Your Sleeve; February 10- March 6, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - The Third Dimension through the Sculptor's Eyes, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Object d'Art: Fine Art in Crafts; November 20- December 30, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Scapes: Land, City, Sea, Undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Reviews, 1976-1979 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Reviews, November 1979- February 1980 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Reviews, 1979-1982 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - "X", Undated (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Artist Outreach; A-H, Undated (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Artist Outreach; J-S, Undated (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Artist Outreach; T-Z, Undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Edith Blum Lecture Series, 1978-1980 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Edith Blum Lecture Series, 1981-1982 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Edith Blum Lecture Series, 1983-1984 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Workshop Outlines, March 6- May 8 1978 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Exhibition Book- Policy and Procedural Manual, Undated (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Exhibitions, October 1977-September 1978 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Exhibitions, 1979-1980 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Lists, 1975-1980 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Gallery Information- Willow Street, Undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Exhibitions, 1981-1982 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Alternative Spaces Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Women Artists News, 1978-1981 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Women Caucus for Art, Undated (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - NEA Artists' Spaces Grant, 1980-1981 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - NEA Grant Request, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Lansburgh Cultural Center Information, Undated (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Works by the Board of Directors, June 3-28 1987 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Exhibitions Documentary, 1976-1977 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - The Muse Exchange Exhibit, May 1-26 1984 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Original Print Calendar, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Slides, Undated (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - WWAC Newsletter, May 1975-December 1979 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - WWAC Newsletter, September 1979-December 1981 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - WWAC Newsletter, January-November 1982 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - WWAC Newsletter, December 1982-April 1985 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 3: Exhibition catalogs and programs, 1976-1987
    Contain printed exhibit catalogs and programs from each exhibit. It also contains programs from other activities at the Center and other institutions.
    - Conference of Women in the Visual Arts, April 20-22, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Sculpture, October 11-29, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Women Choose Women, January 12- February 18, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - A.i.R. Overview- An Exhibition in Two Parts, 1972-1977 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Women Artists Living in Brooklyn, October 11-31, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - From the Center, March 1-27, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Black and White, October 10-28, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - The Creative Line, November 1-19, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Frankel, Moody, Nash, Pfeffer, January 10-28, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Printmakers' Show, April 4-28, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - 14 Hang-ups, May 2-27, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Paintings, September 12- October 7, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Women Artists Year 7, 1977-1978 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Centerwords: An Anthology of Poetry and Prose from WWAC, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Final Draft, May 1-19, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Painting and Sculpture, October 2-27, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Design and Layout: the Graphics Workshop, March 20-April 7, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - New Faces, July 17-August 4, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Printmakers' Show II, October 30- November 24, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Feminist Art - Process and Product, February 26- March 22, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Printmakers' Show III, October 28- November 22, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - The Founders, October 7-25, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Photographs, April 15- May 10, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Portraits for Alice Neel, January 6-24, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Southern Exposure, October 5-23, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - The Eye of May Stevens, January 27-February 21, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Thirty-two Pieces of Paper, June 2-27, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Photography '81, March 24-April 11, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Collage and Drawing, September 8-30, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Art World V, May 12-30, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Woman's Tools, February 24- March 21, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Printmakers' Show IV, February 23- March 20, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Sculpture '82, June 1-26, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - The Goddess Show, February 28-March 31, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Art Auction, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Shape and Texture, April 5-30, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - The Eye of Adelyn Breeskin, March 1- April 2, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Her Own Space, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - The Eye of Eleanor Munro, January 5-23, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Woman as myth and Archetype, May 11-29, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Fiber 82: Miniatures, April 13-May 8, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Let the Art Be First, February 4- March 1, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Talking Pictures, September 7-October 2, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Sculpture to Touch (Braille Catalog), March-April, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Exhibition Lists and Sample Catalogs, 1976-1984 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- Series 8: Audiovisual, 1972-1989
  This series contains slides, videocassettes, audiocassettes, and photographs of exhibits, performances, and other events at the Center.
  - New Art Center "Washington Art" Gallery Talk (2 Copies on Video), March 20, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - "Samhain- A Celebration of Life" by Chanah- New Art center Member (Video), 1988 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - WWAC Conference (3 Reel to Reel Tapes), November 15, 1975 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Washington Review of the Arts (Cassette Tape), April 22, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Diane Brown and Lenore Miller at WWAC (Cassette Tape), Undated (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Washington review of the Arts (Cassette Tape), May 19, 1978 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Star Bullock- New Faces Show at WWAC (Cassette Tape), July 1979 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter Interview (Cassette Tape), March 20, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - American Women in Art (2 Copies on Cassette Tape), 1979 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Judy Chicago Benefit (Cassette Tape), May 19, 1978 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - "Consumer Services" Broadcast incl. R. Tuft Interview and WWAC Workshops and Activities (Cassette Tape), February 27, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Series 9: Memorabilia, undated
  Contains a textile banner with the Center's name and various framed items from the Center's offices. It also includes miscellaneous publications of other arts organizations.
  - Papers, Undated (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Summer Arts Institute at Women's Studio Workshop Catalog of Classes, 1989 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - The Creative Woman: A Report of the Committee of Arts and Humanities, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Women Artist Filmmakers, Undated (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Audrey Levine Glassman: A Retrospective, March 30-April 18, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Printmakers of Washington D.C., March 6-31, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Framed documents, Undated (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Banner, Undated (Box 117, Folder 1)